SOURABHA MISHRA

Accounting Analyst

Accounting Analyst with over 7 years of successful experience in R2R and General accounting.

Excellent experience of handling Technical Tools and Dashboard Reports. Skilled at consolidating and analyzing Financial Data. Highly capable of Budgeting, Financial Forecasting, and Modelling tools.

Contact

Address

Nagawara Bangalore, Karnataka, 560077

Phone

9439642420

E-mail

sourabhamishra.jobs@yaho o.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/sourabha-mishra-950094

Skills

Senior finance analyst

Financial
Reporting
IFRS , USGAAP
, SOX
Month-end
and Year-end
closing
Reconciliation

Work History

2018-01 - Currently on notice

General Accounting Associate

Hudson's Bay Company, Bangalore, Karnataka

- Improved financial operations with careful, indepth analysis and proactive recommendations for improvement by ensuring all activities are comply with IFRS and SOX
- Reviewed and reconciled general ledger accounts and 6 Bank accounts for monthly and year-end reports.
- Improved operational efficiency via automation and increased productivity. (Saved over 1000 hours' time)
- Helped conclusively in assessment of FX
 Exposure of various profit/loss and B/S items to ensure proper hedge.
- Drove implementation of Cadency software to automate reconciliation preparation and review.
- Updating and Maintaining SOP's of various process flows specifically intercompany loans.

2017-03 -2018-01

Sr. Process Associate

Capgemini Technology, Bangalore, Karnataka

Accounts
analysis
R2R
General
Accounting

Software

SAP FICO
Oracle Fusion
Cadency
HFM, Essbase
and
Smartview

Languages



Was a part of financial reporting team, responsible for month-end and year-end closing, reconciliation and different FR related activities

2015-07 - Accountant

2017-02

2014-02

Balaji Mediscans Pvt Ltd, Bhubaneswar, Odisha.

- Compiled general ledger entries on short schedule with 100% accuracy.
- Partnered with auditors to prepare yearly audits and realize compliance with governmental tax guidelines.

2012-04 - Associate Accountant

Sanskruti Associates Pvt Ltd, Bhubaneswar, Odisha

- Managed efficient cash flow reporting, posted cash receipts and analyzed chargebacks, independently addressing and resolving issues.
- Identified, researched and resolved billing variances to maintain system accuracy and currency.

Education

2012-12 - 2014-01	Icwa (intermediate): Cost accountancy ICWAI - Bhubaneswar
2009-06 - 2012-01	Graduation (B.Com): Accounting Utkal University - Cuttack, Odisha

Interests

Cooking and Cricket